Children are hooked on computers.
孩子们沉迷于电脑。
Some spend up to six hours a day on their gadgets.
有些人每天花多达六个小时在电子设备上。
They can be playing games live with others elsewhere in the world, updating their status on social media, texting friends or looking for the latest app to download to their tablets or smartphones.
他们可能在和世界其他地方的人实时玩游戏，在社交媒体上更新状态，给朋友发短信，或者寻找最新的应用程序下载到平板电脑或智能手机上。
This worried Martin Strott.
这让马丁·斯特罗特感到担忧。
He's the headmaster of the Old Hall School in Wellington, in the west of England.
他是英格兰西部惠灵顿老霍尔学校的校长。
He was so concerned that he challenged his students to take part in a week of 'digital detox'.
他非常担心，以至于向学生们发起挑战，让他们参加为期一周的“数字排毒”。
Strott told the local newspaper, the Shropshire Star, that he encourages the pupils to be computer-savvy from a young age, but is concerned that too much screen time will affect the development of their social skills.
斯特罗特告诉当地报纸《什罗普郡星报》，他鼓励学生从小学习电脑知识，但他担心过多的屏幕时间会影响他们社交技能的发展。
He said that this over-reliance on digital devices "erodes family time and they're missing out on messages from body language and facial expressions from those around them".
他说，这种对电子设备的过度依赖“减少了家庭时间，他们没有接收到周围人通过肢体语言和面部表情所传达出来的信息”。
According to the headmaster, the parents are happy with the initiative.
校长表示，家长们对这一倡议感到高兴。
But what about the children?
但孩子们呢？
Nine-year-old Fred usually spends around two hours on his gadgets at home after school and around 12 hours on weekends.
九岁的弗雷德通常放学后在家玩大约两个小时电子设备，周末则大约12个小时。
For him, the digital detox experience was "really hard".
对他来说，数字排毒的经历“非常痛苦”。
Fred spent it playing outside, especially cricket.
弗雷德在排毒期间把时间花在户外活动上，尤其是打板球。
He said that he'll probably engage in different activities from now on but he did miss his phone and online games.
他说，从今以后他可能会参与不同的活动，但他确实很想念他的手机和网络游戏。
The idea of keeping children away from their tech for a while to prevent 'addiction' is not particularly new.
让孩子们暂时远离科技以防止“上瘾”的想法并不新鲜。
There have been similar initiatives in the US.
美国也有类似的举措。
But are they effective in the long run?
但从长远来看，这些举措有效吗？
Well, even if kids go back to their gadgets, the hope is that at least they'll think about how they use their time.
嗯，即使孩子们重新回到电子设备的怀抱，至少希望他们会思考如何利用自己的时间。
What about you: do you spend too many hours hooked on your digital devices?
你呢：你是否花了太多时间沉迷于你的电子设备？